Before I go to bed, I just want to say this to y'all.
I'm not trying to gain favor from the black community.
Y'all respond to some of my posts thinking that I am concerned about like black people in America, you know, distrusting me or not rocking with me or me pissing y'all off.
I don't care. I don't care.
I am only interested in gaining favor with folks who have value systems that align with community, that align with the dismantling of a capitalist system and with the imagining and implementing of how to do that.
I don't care what race, nation or creed you are.
That's all I care about.
So I just feel the need to illuminate that because I'm as proud as I am of my blackness, of which I am deeply aligned and committed to and will always advocate for.
I couldn't give two dams about black people who don't rock with me because I have been forgotten by the black community more times than I can count.
Y'all are not my source of salvation or protection, but I have a community that is much bigger, that is, and that includes black folks.
Look at that.
Ba-dum-ba!
Support a real one.